<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mobile | Dezhi Yu</title><link>https://halfrost.me/tag/mobile/</link><atom:link href="https://halfrost.me/tag/mobile/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Mobile</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© 2024 · Dezhi Yu</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://halfrost.me/images/icon_hu545dc38133db00f2a0f3ba46257a5641_68992_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url><title>Mobile</title><link>https://halfrost.me/tag/mobile/</link></image><item><title>LPDTeam</title><link>https://halfrost.me/project/lpdteam/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://halfrost.me/project/lpdteam/</guid><description/></item><item><title>eleme crowdsource</title><link>https://halfrost.me/project/crowdsource/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://halfrost.me/project/crowdsource/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hummingbird crowdsourcing is waiting for you to join! Create the concept of national distribution, everyone can become a rider and start the distribution life. Produced by Ele.me, the country&amp;rsquo;s largest online ordering platform, a large number of waybills are softened. Easily obtain the waybills of surrounding businesses through the software, grab orders, pick up meals, and deliver meals.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Our advantage:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Based on the brand, no worries about the single quantity&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;ol start="2">
&lt;li>The road is short and easy, with good returns&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;ol start="3">
&lt;li>Level evaluation, exclusive privileges&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Youcai</title><link>https://halfrost.me/project/youcai/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://halfrost.me/project/youcai/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Fangke</title><link>https://halfrost.me/project/fangke/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://halfrost.me/project/fangke/</guid><description/></item><item><title>PingAn YQB</title><link>https://halfrost.me/project/yqb/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://halfrost.me/project/yqb/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Qhome</title><link>https://halfrost.me/project/qhome/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://halfrost.me/project/qhome/</guid><description>&lt;p>Trying to make your home awesome? Download the most innovative and user-friendly smart home app - Qhome by Quatanium Technology Co., Ltd. You will discover that your home could be more intelligent than you ever expected. Everything is awesome!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>With Qhome, you can wirelessly remote:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>• Control lights and appliance on/off switches
• Control curtains, windows and rollers
• Control A/Cs and heaters
• Control any infrared appliances such as TVs, fans, purifiers and etc.
• Control wireless music systems
• Receive change notifications and alerts from home sensors
• Monitor Wi-Fi cameras
• DIY your own customizable scenes
• Schedule action for supported appliances and scenes
• Set trigger rules for automatic environment adjustment
• Share your smart house statistics to social network
• Experience the most convenient way to interact with your home and make your life awesome!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Visit website for more: &lt;a href="http://www.quatanium.com/en">www.quatanium.com/en&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Chinese Dictionary 10001</title><link>https://halfrost.me/project/chinese-dictionary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://halfrost.me/project/chinese-dictionary/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Smart Sokoban</title><link>https://halfrost.me/project/sokoban-smart-android/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://halfrost.me/project/sokoban-smart-android/</guid><description>&lt;p>• This application is mainly to realize the sokoban smart game based on Android. Sokoban smart game(&lt;a href="https://www.sokoban.jp/">https://www.sokoban.jp/&lt;/a>) is an ancient game from Japan. Its design purpose is to train people&amp;rsquo;s logical thinking ability. The game scene is usually set in a small space warehouse, and it is required to place the boxes in the designated location. This requires players to skillfully use limited space and passages, and reasonably arrange the position and movement order of boxes to complete the task.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>• The application is based on Eclipse as a development tool, using Java programming technology, XML technology, Handler technology, and combined with SQLite database to design and implement sokoban smart games. Through the realization and integration of various functional modules, we finally successfully developed a sokoban smart game under the Android platform.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>• The sokoban smart game designed this time allows players to not only enjoy the joy of completing each level, but also store the player’s game records and score, and at the same time share the player’s game results and joy to other people through Weibo, SMS, people web etc.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>